Now let's look at the data of the general insurance industry.
Standard Insurance and
SHII, that is, the standard health insurance
industry, are good leaders. There
may be problems with life insurance, but health and general
insurance will be seen on a strong footing. The
overall health insurance industry is
showing a premium of 28%
in January. Well, the first one or two months before tax filing are very good, but this is a very good data. In fact, if we get general insurance, then the total premium is 19%. So, in January, I am keeping
ICICI Lombard first. All these have been corrected.
I think today, perhaps the
January premium of ICICI Lokmat is
16%. If you
look at Airtel Debt, there is a
20% jump in premium. And in fact, the
market share of ICICI Lombard is increasing in this sector. They are
giving you updates every month. Overall, the
market share is around 24 bps till now. ICC
people tell us that
one leader which has come out is very good, the data of New India
Insurance, the January premium is
42%, so this Airtel Debt
premium has increased only by 6%.
In January, suddenly
its market sale is very strong, now where is this Lunga
industry going tomorrow, it is throwing
out all its blues, but January has been
kept green, yesterday it definitely came into action, so it was
up by 3%, but
when you note the premium figure of 40-45% on your screen,
both of these have been kept green, these
two stocks are the result